vivacashgames.com 2011-12-28

# VivaCashGames.com - Cash Games - Privacy Policy

The Personal Information helps us learn about our members and potential new members. We use this information to improve our services and offer you additional information, assistance and opportunities.

Personal Information includes:

**(a)** Your first and last name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code or postal code, country and state/region in which you live, school name (if applicable), your security question response and password that you choose.

**(b)** When you enter any information, including Personal Information, into any postings, comments, or forums within our Website or WAPsite, we may collect such information and use the same. 

**(c)** When you send us feedback, we may store any information that is contained in your feedback. 

**(d)** When you contact us by sending us an e-mail, we may store your e-mail address and any information contained in the e-mail you send us. 

**(e)** When you sign up to, or win, any campaigns, sweepstakes, or other activities that we make available on our Website or WAPsite, we may store the information designated along with such activity ("Activity Information"). 

The account that you create when you become a member contains Personal Information such as your username, e-mail address and password and only the username is visible to other members of the community of users of the Website or WAPsite. 

All the information in your public profile on the other hand is public information and any member will be able to see it (the "Profile"). Your Profile may contain Personal Information, if you decide to enter such Personal Information into your Profile. 

You may change any of the Personal Information in your account by editing your Profile and/or account, or requesting that we delete your Profile or account. However, do note that we will retain your Personal Information in our archives and in public areas of the site (to the extent you made any public postings).
